* Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

Worldometers.info collects data to deliver the best content, services, and personalized digital ads. We partner with third party advertisers who may use tracking technologies to collect information about your activity on sites and applications across devices, both on our sites and across the Internet.

You always have the choice to experience our website without personalized advertising based on your web browsing activity by visiting the [DAA’s Consumer Choice page](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2#!/), the [NAI's websit](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/)e, and/or the [EU online choices page](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/), from each of your browsers or devices. To avoid personalized advertising based on your mobile app activity, you can install the [DAA’s AppChoices app here](http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices).

**COLLECTION OF DATA**  
Like most standard websites, the site may automatically receive general information that is contained in server log files, such as your internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use, and cookie information. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. Information about how advertising may be served on this site is set forth below.

**USE OF DATA  
**Data may be used to customize and improve your user experience on this site. Efforts will be made to prevent your data from being made available to third parties unless  
(i) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy;  
(ii) your consent is obtained, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out for the sharing of data;  
(iii) a service provided on our site requires interaction with a third party, or is provided by a third party, such as an application service provider; (iv) pursuant to legal action or law enforcement;  
(v) it is found that your use of this site violates the site editor's policy, terms of service, or other usage guidelines, or if it is deemed reasonably necessary by the site editor to protect the site editor's legal rights and/or property;  
or  
(vi) this site is purchased by a third party, in which case that third party will be able to use the data in the same manner as set forth in this policy.

In the event you choose to use links displayed on this website to visit other websites, you are advised to read the privacy policies published on those sites. Worldometers.info uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation to not having this information used by these companies, **click here**.

**COOKIES**  
Like many websites, this website sets and uses cookies to enhance your user experience — to remember your personal settings, for instance. Advertisements may display on this website and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer; such cookies are subject to the privacy policy of the parties providing the advertisement. However, the parties providing the advertising do not have access to this site's cookies. These parties usually use non-personally-identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to this site.

For more information about this type of online advertising, about cookies, and about how to turn this feature off, **please visit this link.**

Please note that turning off advertising cookies won’t mean that you are not served any advertising, merely that it will not be tailored to your interests.

**ADVERTISING**  
This Site is affiliated with Freestar for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site, and Freestar will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. To learn more about Freestar's data usage, click here: [https://freestar.com/privacy-policy/.](https://freestar.com/privacy-policy/)  
  
**WEBSITE USAGE STATISTICS**  
**Google Analytics**  
We use Google Analytics, which is Google’s analytics tool that helps websites to understand how their visitors engage with their web properties. It may use a set of cookies to collect information and report website usage statistics without personally identifying individual visitors. The main cookie used by Google Analytics is the ‘\_ga’ cookie. In addition to reporting website usage statistics, Google Analytics can also be used, together with some of the advertising cookies described below, to help show more relevant ads on Google properties (like Google Search) and across the web and to measure interactions with the ads shown by Google. Learn more about [how Google uses data when you use this websit](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)e and about [Analytics cookies and privacy information.](https://developers.google.com/analytics/resources/concepts/gaConceptsCookies?hl=en)  

**Google/Doubleclick  
**We partner with Google Adsense and Google/Doubleclick to display the advertising that pays for this website. For that to work effectively they will use cookies to store data and access data about your use of this website. You can learn more about how Google use this data and how to opt out if you choose [here](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites?hl=en)

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Worldometers.info. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Worldometers.info visitors based on their visit to Worldometers.info and other sites on the Internet. You can opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads).

**Other third party advertisers  
**Advertisers who will have access to data we collect on this site may include: GoogleAdX, Freestar, AppNexus, IndexExchange, OpenX RhythmOne, DistrictM, RubiconProject, Sovrn, Conversant, Amazon, Sharethrough, EMX, SublimeSkinz, JustPremium, LKQD, Telaria, AnswerMedia, Pubmatic, bluTonic, ROIMedia, Aerserv, Lockerdome, Consumable, Beachfront, Gumgum, Triplelift, Media.net, BounceX, Undertone, Powerlinks, Nativo, NativoVideo, advertising.com, 33Across, Teads, and Unruly.

**Cookies and web beacons**  
Our site does not use cookies. However, we use outside companies to display ads on our site and to collect statistics about web visitors. These companies may be placing and reading cookies on your web browser, or using web beacons to collect information. Remember that cookies do not allow anyone to access your private information on your computer. They only record information about your visits to a web site. Cookies may be used tfor personalization of ads but can be also used for non-personalized advertising.  
  
**Cookie management**  
It is important to know that if you disable cookies you may not be able to use certain features offered by some web sites. You can disable cookies through your browser. Most browsers have instructions on how to disable cookies in their "Help" sections. The instructions for all browsers vary. But the steps are generally similar for most. Here are some places you can look to disable or enable cookies:

* Internet Explorer: Look in the Tools menu, select Internet Options, and then click the Security tab. Click Internet, and then click Custom Level. Scroll down to Cookies, click disable (or enable) for both cookie options, and then click OK.  
    
* Mozilla Firefox: Open Tasks, choose Privacy & Security, and then Cookie Manager. Choose View Stored Cookies from the submenu to open the Cookie Manager window. Select one or more cookies and click either Remove Cookie or Remove All Cookies.  
    
* Netscape: Select Edit | Preferences from the main menu. Select Advanced and under Cookies, select Disable cookies and click OK.  
    
* Safari: Choose Preferences from the Safari menu and click Security. Select Never, Always, or Only from sites you navigate to, to set your preferences at the level you desire. To see the cookies stored on your computer, click Show Cookies. From here you have the option to remove one or two cookies or all cookies.

**Worldometer newsletter  
**Worldometers.info maintains a strict "no-spam" policy. Shall you decide to sign up to Worldometer'ss free periodic newsletter, we will only use your email address only to send you Worldometer'ss newsletter. Your e-mail address will not be sold to a third party. You have the option to unsubscribe from our newsletter at any time.

**Approval  
**By approving and using our website, you agree that we and our third party advertisers can:

* transfer your personal data to the United States or other countries, and
* process your personal data to serve you with personalized ads, subject to your choices as described above and in our privacy policy.

© Copyright Worldometers.info - All rights reserved - [Disclaimer & Privacy Policy](https://www.worldometers.info/disclaimer/)
